OLEH RUSIN

TRAINEE/JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER (REACT)

LVIV: OFFICE / REMOTE WORK

SUMMARY

I study front-end development. I have knowledge in web development such as: JavaScript, HTML/CSS, React, in addition - the basics of Python and GIT. I am passionate about web development and want to actively develop in it. My education - Master`s degree of system programming. I like teamwork and have experience in managing teams.



PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

Programming languages: JavaScript,

React.js, Python basics.

Technologies: HTML5, CSS3, SCSS. **IDE:** VSCode, PyCharm, Chrome dev

tools.

Other: GIT, npm.

English: Pre-Intermediate.

Ukrainian: Native.

SOFT SKILLS

I perform tasks responsibly and perfectly. I like to work in teams. I have the skills of a mentor, manager and leader. I am able to resolve conflicts, find solutions to different situations. My values are kindness, sincerity and openness.

EDUCATION

Volodymyr Dahl East Ukrainian National University

Master's degree, System Programming 2008-2013

CONTACTS

Lviv, Ukraine +380661494321

<u>oleg.o.rusin@gmail.com</u> <u>LinkedIn</u> <u>Telegram</u>

MY PROJECTS

Blog about coffee - GitHub-link

Website with responsive layout, various sections and menus, a contact form, and an attractive design. **HTML, SCSS, CSS, JS**

PingPong - GitHub-link

2D mini-game created in native JS using canvas. JS, HTML, CSS

SELF-EDUCATION

(9/2022 - PRESENT)

ITVDN - online school of programming

- JavaScript Starter (certificate) / JavaScript Essential (certificate)
- React Essential (certificate)
- HTML5/CSS3 Starter (certificate)
- GIT Basics (<u>certificate</u>).
- Python Starter/Essential (certificate).

Other

Codewars.com, stackoverflow.com, developer.mozilla.org, leetcode.com, uk.javascript.info, DOU

EXPERIENCE

Manager/Administrator

Restaurants SushiMaster, NOA | Lviv | 09/2021 - 11/2022 (1 year 3 months)

Responsibilities:

Organization and control of the restaurant. Reports and analytics, impact on financial and rating indicators, withdrawal from the crisis state. Training and selection of staff.

Owner/Director

Coffee house "Holiday club" | **Lysychansk** | 11/2016 - 05/2021 (4 years 6 months)

Responsibilities:

Personally managed everything from the creation phase of business idea, raising investment, opening and sustainable development. Mastered the skills of developing of the institution from "0" and management.